[
{"Front": "会う", "Back": "あう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "青", "Back": "あお", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "青い", "Back": "あおい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "赤", "Back": "あか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "赤い", "Back": "あかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "明い", "Back": "あかるい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "秋", "Back": "あき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "開く", "Back": "あく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "開ける", "Back": "あける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "上げる", "Back": "あげる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "朝", "Back": "あさ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "朝御飯", "Back": "あさごはん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "足", "Back": "あし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "明日", "Back": "あした", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "遊ぶ", "Back": "あそぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "暖かい", "Back": "あたたかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "頭", "Back": "あたま", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "新しい", "Back": "あたらしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "暑い", "Back": "あつい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "熱い", "Back": "あつい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "厚い", "Back": "あつい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "後", "Back": "あと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "兄", "Back": "あに", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "姉", "Back": "あね", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "危ない", "Back": "あぶない", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "甘い", "Back": "あまい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "雨", "Back": "あめ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "飴", "Back": "あめ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "洗う", "Back": "あらう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "歩く", "Back": "あるく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "言う", "Back": "いう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "家", "Back": "いえ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "行く", "Back": "いく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "池", "Back": "いけ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "医者", "Back": "いしゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "忙しい", "Back": "いそがしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "痛い", "Back": "いたい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一", "Back": "いち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一日", "Back": "いちにち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "五日", "Back": "いつか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一緒", "Back": "いっしょ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "五つ", "Back": "いつつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "犬", "Back": "いぬ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "今", "Back": "いま", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "意味", "Back": "いみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "妹", "Back": "いもうと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "嫌", "Back": "いや", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "入口", "Back": "いりぐち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "居る", "Back": "いる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "要る", "Back": "いる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "入れる", "Back": "いれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "色", "Back": "いろ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "上", "Back": "うえ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "後ろ", "Back": "うしろ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "薄い", "Back": "うすい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "歌", "Back": "うた", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "歌う", "Back": "うたう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "生まれる", "Back": "うまれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "海", "Back": "うみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "売る", "Back": "うる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "煩い", "Back": "うるさい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "上着", "Back": "うわぎ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "絵", "Back": "え", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "映画", "Back": "えいが", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "映画館", "Back": "えいがかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "英語", "Back": "えいご", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "駅", "Back": "えき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "鉛筆", "Back": "えんぴつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "多い", "Back": "おおい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大きい", "Back": "おおきい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大きな", "Back": "おおきな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大勢", "Back": "おおぜい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お母さん", "Back": "おかあさん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お菓子", "Back": "おかし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お金", "Back": "おかね", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "起きる", "Back": "おきる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "置く", "Back": "おく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "奥さん", "Back": "おくさん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お酒", "Back": "おさけ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お皿", "Back": "おさら", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "伯父/叔父", "Back": "おじいさん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "教える", "Back": "おしえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "押す", "Back": "おす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "遅い", "Back": "おそい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お茶", "Back": "おちゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お手洗い", "Back": "おてあらい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お父さん", "Back": "おとうさん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "弟", "Back": "おとうと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "男", "Back": "おとこ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "男の子", "Back": "おとこのこ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一昨日", "Back": "おととい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一昨年", "Back": "おととし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大人", "Back": "おとな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "同じ", "Back": "おなじ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お兄さん", "Back": "おにいさん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お姉さん", "Back": "おねえさん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "伯母さん/叔母さん", "Back": "おばさん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お風呂", "Back": "おふろ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お弁当", "Back": "おべんとう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "覚える", "Back": "おぼえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "重い", "Back": "おもい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "泳ぐ", "Back": "およぐ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "降りる", "Back": "おりる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "終る", "Back": "おわる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "音楽", "Back": "おんがく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "女", "Back": "おんな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "女の子", "Back": "おんなのこ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "外国", "Back": "がいこく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "外国人", "Back": "がいこくじん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "会社", "Back": "かいしゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "階段", "Back": "かいだん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "買い物", "Back": "かいもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "買う", "Back": "かう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "返す", "Back": "かえす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "帰る", "Back": "かえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "書く", "Back": "かく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "学生", "Back": "がくせい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "傘", "Back": "かさ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "貸す", "Back": "かす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "風", "Back": "かぜ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "風邪", "Back": "かぜ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "家族", "Back": "かぞく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "方", "Back": "かた", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "学校", "Back": "がっこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "家庭", "Back": "かてい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "角", "Back": "かど", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "花瓶", "Back": "かびん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "紙", "Back": "かみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "火曜日", "Back": "かようび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "辛い", "Back": "からい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "体", "Back": "からだ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "借りる", "Back": "かりる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "軽い", "Back": "かるい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "川/河", "Back": "かわ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "漢字", "Back": "かんじ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "木", "Back": "き", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "黄色", "Back": "きいろ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "黄色い", "Back": "きいろい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "消える", "Back": "きえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "聞く", "Back": "きく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "北", "Back": "きた", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "汚い", "Back": "きたない", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "喫茶店", "Back": "きっさてん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "切手", "Back": "きって", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "切符", "Back": "きっぷ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "昨日", "Back": "きのう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "九", "Back": "きゅう / く", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "牛肉", "Back": "ぎゅうにく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "牛乳", "Back": "ぎゅうにゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "今日", "Back": "きょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "教室", "Back": "きょうしつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "兄弟", "Back": "きょうだい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "去年", "Back": "きょねん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "嫌い", "Back": "きらい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "切る", "Back": "きる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "着る", "Back": "きる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "銀行", "Back": "ぎんこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "金曜日", "Back": "きんようび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "薬", "Back": "くすり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "果物", "Back": "くだもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "口", "Back": "くち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "靴", "Back": "くつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "靴下", "Back": "くつした", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "国", "Back": "くに", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "曇り", "Back": "くもり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "曇る", "Back": "くもる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "暗い", "Back": "くらい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "来る", "Back": "くる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "車", "Back": "くるま", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "黒", "Back": "くろ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "黒い", "Back": "くろい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "警官", "Back": "けいかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "今朝", "Back": "けさ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "消す", "Back": "けす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "結構", "Back": "けっこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "結婚", "Back": "けっこん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "月曜日", "Back": "げつようび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "玄関", "Back": "げんかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "元気", "Back": "げんき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "五", "Back": "ご", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "公園", "Back": "こうえん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "交差点", "Back": "こうさてん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "紅茶", "Back": "こうちゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "交番", "Back": "こうばん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "声", "Back": "こえ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "午後", "Back": "ごご", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "九日", "Back": "ここのか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "九つ", "Back": "ここのつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "午前", "Back": "ごぜん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "答える", "Back": "こたえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "今年", "Back": "ことし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "言葉", "Back": "ことば", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "子供", "Back": "こども", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "御飯", "Back": "ごはん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "困る", "Back": "こまる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "今月", "Back": "こんげつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "今週", "Back": "こんしゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "今晩", "Back": "こんばん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "財布", "Back": "さいふ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "魚", "Back": "さかな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "先", "Back": "さき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "咲く", "Back": "さく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "作文", "Back": "さくぶん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "差す", "Back": "さす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "雑誌", "Back": "ざっし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "砂糖", "Back": "さとう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "寒い", "Back": "さむい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "さ来年", "Back": "さらいねん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "三", "Back": "さん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "散歩", "Back": "さんぽする", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "四", "Back": "し / よん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "塩", "Back": "しお", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "時間", "Back": "じかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "仕事", "Back": "しごと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "辞書", "Back": "じしょ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "静か", "Back": "しずか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "下", "Back": "した", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "七", "Back": "しち / なな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "質問", "Back": "しつもん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "自転車", "Back": "じてんしゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "自動車", "Back": "じどうしゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "死ぬ", "Back": "しぬ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "字引", "Back": "じびき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "自分", "Back": "じぶん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "閉まる", "Back": "しまる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "閉める", "Back": "しめる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "締める", "Back": "しめる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "写真", "Back": "しゃしん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "十", "Back": "じゅう&nbsp;&nbsp;とお", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "授業", "Back": "じゅぎょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "宿題", "Back": "しゅくだい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "上手", "Back": "じょうず", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "丈夫", "Back": "じょうぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "食堂", "Back": "しょくどう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "知る", "Back": "しる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "白", "Back": "しろ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "白い", "Back": "しろい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "新聞", "Back": "しんぶん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "水曜日", "Back": "すいようび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "吸う", "Back": "すう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "好き", "Back": "すき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "少ない", "Back": "すくない", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "少し", "Back": "すこし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "涼しい", "Back": "すずしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "住む", "Back": "すむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "座る", "Back": "すわる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "背", "Back": "せ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "生徒", "Back": "せいと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "背広", "Back": "せびろ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "狭い", "Back": "せまい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "千", "Back": "せん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "先月", "Back": "せんげつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "先週", "Back": "せんしゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "先生", "Back": "せんせい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "洗濯", "Back": "せんたく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "全部", "Back": "ぜんぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "掃除", "Back": "そうじする", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "外", "Back": "そと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "空", "Back": "そら", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大学", "Back": "だいがく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大使館", "Back": "たいしかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大丈夫", "Back": "だいじょうぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大好き", "Back": "だいすき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大切", "Back": "たいせつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "台所", "Back": "だいどころ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "高い", "Back": "たかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "出す", "Back": "だす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "立つ", "Back": "たつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "建物", "Back": "たてもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "楽しい", "Back": "たのしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "頼む", "Back": "たのむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "食べ物", "Back": "たべもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "食べる", "Back": "たべる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "卵", "Back": "たまご", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "誰", "Back": "だれ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "誕生日", "Back": "たんじょうび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "小さい", "Back": "ちいさい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "小さな", "Back": "ちいさな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "近い", "Back": "ちかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "違う", "Back": "ちがう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "近く", "Back": "ちかく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "地下鉄", "Back": "ちかてつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "地図", "Back": "ちず", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "茶色", "Back": "ちゃいろ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "使う", "Back": "つかう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "疲れる", "Back": "つかれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "次", "Back": "つぎ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "着く", "Back": "つく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "机", "Back": "つくえ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "作る", "Back": "つくる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "勤める", "Back": "つとめる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "冷たい", "Back": "つめたい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "強い", "Back": "つよい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "手", "Back": "て", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "出かける", "Back": "でかける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "手紙", "Back": "てがみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "出口", "Back": "でぐち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "出る", "Back": "でる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "天気", "Back": "てんき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "電気", "Back": "でんき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "電車", "Back": "でんしゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "電話", "Back": "でんわ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "戸", "Back": "と", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "動物", "Back": "どうぶつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "遠い", "Back": "とおい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "十日", "Back": "とおか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "時々", "Back": "ときどき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "時計", "Back": "とけい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "所", "Back": "ところ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "年", "Back": "とし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "図書館", "Back": "としょかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "隣", "Back": "となり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "飛ぶ", "Back": "とぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "止まる", "Back": "とまる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "友達", "Back": "ともだち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "土曜日", "Back": "どようび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "鳥", "Back": "とり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "とり肉", "Back": "とりにく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "取る", "Back": "とる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "撮る", "Back": "とる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "中", "Back": "なか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "長い", "Back": "ながい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "鳴く", "Back": "なく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "無くす", "Back": "なくす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "夏", "Back": "なつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "夏休み", "Back": "なつやすみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "七つ", "Back": "ななつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "七日", "Back": "なのか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "名前", "Back": "なまえ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "習う", "Back": "ならう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "並ぶ", "Back": "ならぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "並べる", "Back": "ならべる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "何", "Back": "なん/なに", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "二", "Back": "に", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "賑やか", "Back": "にぎやか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "肉", "Back": "にく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "西", "Back": "にし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "日曜日", "Back": "にちようび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "荷物", "Back": "にもつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "庭", "Back": "にわ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "脱ぐ", "Back": "ぬぐ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "温い", "Back": "ぬるい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "猫", "Back": "ねこ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "寝る", "Back": "ねる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "登る", "Back": "のぼる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "飲み物", "Back": "のみもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "飲む", "Back": "のむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "乗る", "Back": "のる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "歯", "Back": "は", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "灰皿", "Back": "はいざら", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "入る", "Back": "はいる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "葉書", "Back": "はがき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "箱", "Back": "はこ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "始まる", "Back": "はじまる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "橋", "Back": "はし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "初め/始め", "Back": "はじめ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "初めて", "Back": "はじめて", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "走る", "Back": "はしる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "二十歳", "Back": "はたち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "働く", "Back": "はたらく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "八", "Back": "はち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "二十日", "Back": "はつか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "花", "Back": "はな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "鼻", "Back": "はな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "話", "Back": "はなし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "話す", "Back": "はなす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "早い", "Back": "はやい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "速い", "Back": "はやい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "春", "Back": "はる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "貼る", "Back": "はる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "晴れ", "Back": "はれ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "晴れる", "Back": "はれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "半", "Back": "はん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "晩", "Back": "ばん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "番号", "Back": "ばんごう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "晩御飯", "Back": "ばんごはん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "半分", "Back": "はんぶん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "東", "Back": "ひがし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "引く", "Back": "ひく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "弾く", "Back": "ひく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "低い", "Back": "ひくい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "飛行機", "Back": "ひこうき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "左", "Back": "ひだり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "人", "Back": "ひと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一つ", "Back": "ひとつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一月", "Back": "ひとつき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一人", "Back": "ひとり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "暇", "Back": "ひま", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "百", "Back": "ひゃく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "病院", "Back": "びょういん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "病気", "Back": "びょうき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "昼", "Back": "ひる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "昼御飯", "Back": "ひるごはん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "広い", "Back": "ひろい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "封筒", "Back": "ふうとう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "吹く", "Back": "ふく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "服", "Back": "ふく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "二つ", "Back": "ふたつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "豚肉", "Back": "ぶたにく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "二人", "Back": "ふたり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "二日", "Back": "ふつか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "太い", "Back": "ふとい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "冬", "Back": "ふゆ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "降る", "Back": "ふる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "古い", "Back": "ふるい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "文章", "Back": "ぶんしょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "下手", "Back": "へた", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "部屋", "Back": "へや", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "辺", "Back": "へん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "勉強", "Back": "べんきょうする", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "便利", "Back": "べんり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "帽子", "Back": "ぼうし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "欲しい", "Back": "ほしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "細い", "Back": "ほそい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "本", "Back": "ほん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "本棚", "Back": "ほんだな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "毎朝", "Back": "まいあさ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "毎月", "Back": "まいげつ/まいつき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "毎週", "Back": "まいしゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "毎日", "Back": "まいにち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "毎年", "Back": "まいねん/まいとし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "毎晩", "Back": "まいばん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "前", "Back": "まえ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "曲る", "Back": "まがる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "町", "Back": "まち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "待つ", "Back": "まつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "窓", "Back": "まど", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "丸い/円い", "Back": "まるい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "万", "Back": "まん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "万年筆", "Back": "まんねんひつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "磨く", "Back": "みがく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "右", "Back": "みぎ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "短い", "Back": "みじかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "水", "Back": "みず", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "店", "Back": "みせ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "見せる", "Back": "みせる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "道", "Back": "みち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "三日", "Back": "みっか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "三つ", "Back": "みっつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "緑", "Back": "みどり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "皆さん", "Back": "みなさん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "南", "Back": "みなみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "耳", "Back": "みみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "見る&nbsp;&nbsp;観る", "Back": "みる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "六日", "Back": "むいか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "向こう", "Back": "むこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "難しい", "Back": "むずかしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "六つ", "Back": "むっつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "村", "Back": "むら", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "目", "Back": "め", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "眼鏡", "Back": "めがね", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "もう一度", "Back": "もういちど", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "木曜日", "Back": "もくようび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "持つ", "Back": "もつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "物", "Back": "もの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "門", "Back": "もん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "問題", "Back": "もんだい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "八百屋", "Back": "やおや", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "野菜", "Back": "やさい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "易しい", "Back": "やさしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "安い", "Back": "やすい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "休み", "Back": "やすみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "休む", "Back": "やすむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "八つ", "Back": "やっつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "山", "Back": "やま", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "夕方", "Back": "ゆうがた", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "夕飯", "Back": "ゆうはん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "郵便局", "Back": "ゆうびんきょく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "昨夜", "Back": "ゆうべ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "有名", "Back": "ゆうめい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "雪", "Back": "ゆき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "八日", "Back": "ようか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "洋服", "Back": "ようふく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "横", "Back": "よこ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "四日", "Back": "よっか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "四つ", "Back": "よっつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "呼ぶ", "Back": "よぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "読む", "Back": "よむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "夜", "Back": "よる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "弱い", "Back": "よわい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "来月", "Back": "らいげつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "来週", "Back": "らいしゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "来年", "Back": "らいねん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "留学生", "Back": "りゅうがくせい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "両親", "Back": "りょうしん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "料理", "Back": "りょうり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "旅行", "Back": "りょこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "零", "Back": "れい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "冷蔵庫", "Back": "れいぞうこ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "練習", "Back": "れんしゅうする", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "廊下", "Back": "ろうか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "六", "Back": "ろく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "若い", "Back": "わかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "分かる", "Back": "わかる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "忘れる", "Back": "わすれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "私", "Back": "わたくし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "渡す", "Back": "わたす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "渡る", "Back": "わたる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "悪い", "Back": "わるい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n5-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{}]
